# noinspection SpellCheckingInspection
question_data = [
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Chickens can live without a head.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Hippopotomonstrosesquippedaliophobia is the irrational fear of long words.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The planet Mars has two moons orbiting it.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Like with the Neanderthals, Homo sapiens sapiens also interbred with the Denisovans.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shrimp can swim backwards.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In the periodic table, Potassium&#039;s symbol is the letter K.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "question": "Sugar contains fat.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Pneumonoultramicroscopicsilicovolcanoconiosis is a synonym for the disease known as silicosis.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Sound can travel through a vacuum.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Science & Nature", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "&quot;Tachycardia&quot; or &quot;Tachyarrhythmia&quot; refers to a resting heart-rate near or over "
                 "100 BPM.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
